http://www.lrse.com/pages/privacy-policy

/
Privacy Policy - LRSE Life Raft + Survival Equipment, Inc.
PRIVACY POLICY
At LRSE we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use LRSE's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
The LRSE Website contains links to external Websites. LRSE is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of those sites not housed on LRSE servers.
In addition to information actively provided by individuals using LRSE's Websites, the LRSE web servers routinely record the following information each time the sites are used:
Internet address of the computer being used
Web pages requested
Network software access
Referring web page
Browser used
Passwords and accounts accessed
Volume of data storage and transfers
Server space used for e-mail
LRSE uses this information to monitor and preserve the functioning and integrity of the system. In cases of suspected violations of LRSE's policies, especially unauthorized access to computing systems, the system administrator concerned may authorize detailed session logging. This may involve capturing and retaining a complete keystroke log of an entire session. In addition, a system administrator for the equipment involved may authorize limited searching of user files on individual or networked computers to gather evidence on a suspected violation.
Disclosure Of Information
LRSE does not sell or distribute confidential information it collects online to individuals or entities not affiliated with the division.
Security
Although every effort is made to secure network communications, LRSE. cannot ensure the privacy of online communications. Individuals using online services should also take steps to protect personal information, such as closing the web browser when finished using the site. Failure to do so may result in personal information being viewed by someone else using the same computer.
